A Finding Aid to the Cecilia Beaux Papers, 1863-1968, in the Archives of American Art AAA.beauceci
Archives of American Art
- Photographs, circa 1888-1919; Series 6; 0.3 Linear feet Box 3
  - Green Alley, Gloucester, Massachusetts, after 1905, undated; (4 folders, including vintage prints, recent prints from discarded nitrate, duplicates, and copies) (Box 3, Folder 34-37)
    (Several pictures depict Beaux outside her home, alone and with others who are unidentified)
  - Beaux's Family Members, undated; (3 folders, including vintage prints, recent prints from discarded nitrate, and copies) (Box 3, Folder 38-40)
    (Pictured are Beaux's nephew Harry Drinker and her Aunt Eliza)
  - John Singer Sargent, 1903; (2 folders, including copies) (Box 3, Folder 41-42)
  - Unidentified Woman, undated (Box 3, Folder 43)
  - Photographs of Works of Art, Installation Views, undated (Box 3, Folder 44)
  - Photographs of Works of Art, undated; (3 folders, including copies; not scanned) (Box 3, Folder 45)